RG 015, Office of Policy and Management
Connecticut State Library
- Series 5. Finance Advisory Committee, 1943-1981; 1983-003; 50.5 cubic feet
  - Budget allotment or adjustment requests, 1943-1981
    - Budget adjustments
      - 1966 November 4-December 19, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1966 December 19-1967 February 14, 1 volume (Box 24)
      - 1967 February 14-April 4, 1 volume (Box 24)
      - 1967 April 4-May 16, 1 volume (Box 24)
      - 1967 May 16-June 30, 1 volume (Box 24)
      - 1967 July 5-20, 1 volume (Box 24)
      - 1966 August 1-30, 1 volume (Box 24)
      - 1967 September 1-28, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1967 October 3-31, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1967 November 1-30, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1967 December 1-27, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1968 January 2-31, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1968 February 5-29, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1968 March 5-29, 1 volume (Box 26)
      - 1968 April 2-30, 1 volume (Box 26)
      - 1968 May 2-31, 1 volume (Box 26)
      - 1968 June 5-26, 1 volume (Box 26)
      - 1968 July 2-31, 1 volume (Box 26)
      - 1968 August 7-September 4, 1 volume (Box 26)
      - 1968 September 4-27, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1968 October 1-31, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1968 November 1-27, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1968 December 2-31, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1969 January 3-28, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1969 January 28-February 18, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1969 February 18-March 18, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1969 March 4-18, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1969 March 4-April 21, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1969 April 21-May 13, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1969 May 13-June 6, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1969 June 6-30, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1969 July 1-28, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1969 July 28-August 18, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1969 August 18-September 9, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1969 September 9-29, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1969 October 3-23, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1969 October 23-November 18, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - 1969 November 18-December 5, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1969 December 5-1970 January 5, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1970 January 5-29, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1970 February 3-24, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1970 February 24-March 16, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1970 March 16-April 13, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1970 April 13-30, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1970 March 16-April 13, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1970 May 27-June 16, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1970 June 16-July 8, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1970 July 8-28, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1970 July 28-August 4, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1970 August 4-September 2, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1970 September 2-21, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1970 September 21-October 8, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1970 October 9-28, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1970 October 28-November 17, 1 volume (Box 32)
      - 1970 November 17-December 8, 1 volume (Box 33)
      - 1970 December 8-January 4, 1 volume (Box 33)
      - 1971 January 4-February 8, 1 volume (Box 33)
      - 1971 February 8-18, 1 volume (Box 33)
      - 1971 February 18-March 4, 1 volume (Box 33)
      - 1971 March 4-12, 1 volume (Box 34)
      - 1971 March 12-April 6, 1 volume (Box 34)
      - 1971 April 6-May 3, 1 volume (Box 34)
      - 1971 May 3, 1 volume (Box 34)
      - 1971 May 3-10, 1 volume (Box 34)
      - 1971 May 11-26, 1 volume (Box 34)
      - 1971 May 26-June 10, 1 volume (Box 35)
      - 1971 June 10-23, 1 volume (Box 35)
      - 1971 June 23-July 13, 1 volume (Box 35)
      - 1971 July 13-21, 1 volume (Box 35)
      - 1971 July 21-August 9, 1 volume (Box 35)
      - 1971 August 9, 1 volume (Box 35)
      - 1971 August 9-30, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 August 30-September 20, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 September 20-28, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 September 28-30, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 October 1-20, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 October 20-27, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 October 27-November 2, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 November 2-24, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 November 24-December 6, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 December 6-17, 1 volume (Box 36)
      - 1971 December 17-21, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1971 December 21-1972 January 5, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1972 January 5-19, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1972 January 19-31, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1972 February 2-10, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1972 February 10-28, 1 volume (Box 37)
      - 1972 Februaru 28-March 9, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 March 9-29, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 April 3-10, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 April 10-20, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 April 20-May 4, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 May 4-19, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 May 19-June 1, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 June 1-19, 1 volume (Box 38)
      - 1972 June 19-26, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1972 June 29-July 18, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1972 July 18-August 4, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1972 August 4-24, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1972 August 24-September 7, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1972 September 7-18, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1970 September 18-28, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1972 October 2-19, 1 volume (Box 39)
      - 1972 October 19-November 10, 1 volume (Box 40)
      - 1972 November 10-December 1, 1 volume (Box 40)
      - 1972 December 1-December 18, 1 volume (Box 40)
      - 1972 December 20-27, 1 volume (Box 40)
      - 1973 January 4-12, 1 volume (Box 40)
        Starting with 1973 individual volumes are no longer numbered and therefore not listed individually.
      - 1973 January 16-March 15, 4 volumes (Box 40)
      - 1973 March 16-June 29, 8 volumes (Box 41)
      - 1973 March 16-June 19, 8 volumes (Box 42)
      - 1973 June 20-September 18, 9 volumes (Box 42)
      - 1973 September 21-December 18, 9 volumes (Box 43)
      - 1973 December 20- 1974 March 8, 1974 March 27-April 5, 6 volumes (Box 44)
      - 1974 March 11-25, April 8-June 10, 5 volumes (Box 45)
      - 1974 June 12-August 14, 5 volumes (Box 46)
      - 1974 August 19-November 25, 9 volumes (Box 47)
      - 1974 November 26-1975 March 7, 6 volumes (Box 48)
      - 1975 March 10-June 11, 5 volumes (Box 49)
      - 1973 June 12-November 7, 7 volumes (Box 50)
      - 1975 November 10-December 2, 1 volume (Box 51)
      - 1975 December 3-1976 March 3, 8 volumes (Box 52)
      - 1976 March 3-July 8, 9 volumes (Box 53)
      - 1976 July 8-November 29, 8 volumes (Box 54)
      - 1976 November 29-1977 May 24, 9 volumes (Box 55)
      - 1977 May 24-September 26, 8 volumes (Box 56)
      - 1977 September 26-1978 March 27, 11 volumes (Box 57)
      - 1978 March 28-September 11, 11 volumes (Box 58)
      - 1978 September 11-1979 March 1, 11 volumes (Box 59)
      - 1979 March 1-August 7, 12 volumes (Box 60)
      - 1979 August 9-1980 March 28, 12 volumes (Box 61)
      - 1980 March 28-October 28, 12 volumes (Box 62)
      - 1980 November 3-1981 June 12, 10 volumes (Box 63)
      - 1981 June 18-December 30, 7 volumes (Box 64)
- Series 6. Special Bond Commission, 1941-1967; 1983-003
  - Minutes, 1941-1967
    - Bradley Field Bond Commission (Box 8, Volume 1)
    - Expressway Bond Commission (Box 8, Volume 1)
    - Humane and Welfare Building Program Bond Commission (Box 8, Volume 1)
    - Institutional Buildings and Capital Improvements (Box 8, Volume 1)
    - Bradley Field Bond Commission (Box 8, Volume 1)
    - Redevelopment Committee (Box 8, Volume 2)
    - Committee Created by Section 8-86, Housing Mortgage Bonds (Box 8, Volume 2)
    - Bond Issues for Connecticut State Teachers Colleges and Vocational Schools (Box 8, Volume 2)
    - University of Connecticut Bond Commission (Box 8, Volume 2)
    - Committee Created under Chapter 52, Moderate Rental Housing (Box 8, Volume 2)
- Series 7. State Bond Commission, 1953-1988; 9 cubic feet
  - Minutes, 1953-1977; 1983-003
    - 1953 July 22-1961 January 27, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1961 April 27-1962 August 29, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1962 September 12-1963 December 26, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1964 February 13-1965 May 27, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1965 July 13-1966 March 29, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1966 June 7-1967 May 4, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1967 June 13-1968 January 18, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - 1968 February 15-August 15, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - 1968 September 19-1969 January 16, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - 1969 February 20-July 17, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - 1969 August 21-December 18, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - 1970 January 15-May 21, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - 1967 June 13-1968 January 18, 1 volume (Box 14)
    - 1970 June 8-November 19, 1 volume (Box 14)
    - 1970 December 18-1971 April 23, 1 volume (Box 14)
    - 1971 May 28-October 22, 1 volume (Box 14)
    - 1971 November 19-1972 April 28, 1 volume (Box 14)
    - 1972 May 26-September 22, 1 volume (Box 14)
    - 1972 October 27-1973 June 22, 1 volume (Box 14)
    - 1973 July 27-1974 January 25, 1 volume (Box 15)
    - 1974 February 22-June 28, 1 volume (Box 15)
    - 1974 July 26-November 22, 1 volume (Box 15)
    - 1974 December 27-1975 October 24, 1 volume (Box 15)
    - 1975 December 12-1976 September 17, 1 volume (Box 16)
    - 1977 July 21-1978 January 27, 1 volume (Box 16)
  - Hearing Files, 1987-1988; 1995-013
    - Bond Bills for 1987 Session (Box 1)
    - 1987 Bonding Priority List (Box 1)
    - Bonding Notes for 1987 (Box 1)
    - Bond [illegible], 1987 (Box 1)
    - Governor's Capital Budget, 1987 (Box 1)
    - 1987 Transportation Committee Bonding Transcripts (Box 1)
    - 1987 Environment Committee Bonding Transcripts (Box 1)
    - Board of Governor's of Higher Education material, 4 inches (Box 1)
    - Department of Agriculture, 1987 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Department of Economic Development / Connecticut Product & Development Corp., 1987 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Office of Policy & Management, 1987 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Bond meeting, 1987 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Marketing Authority, 1987 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1987 March 5 (Box 1)
    - Department of Corrections, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Department of Human Resources, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Military Department, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Judicial Department, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Bonding Subcommittee Meeting, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Department of Transportation, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Department of Public Safety, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Department of Children & Youth Services, 1987 March 10 (Box 1)
    - Bonding Meeting, 1987 March 19 (Box 1)
    - American School for the Deaf, 1987 March 19 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Historical Commission, 1987 March 19 (Box 1)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - Department of Mental Health, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Alcohol & Drug Abuse Commission, 1987 march 19 (Box 2)
    - Commission on Fire Prevention & Control, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Public Broadcasting, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - Department of Mental Retardation, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut State Library, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Board of Education & Services to the Blind, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - State Board of Education, 1987 March 19 (Box 2)
    - State Technical Colleges, 1987 March 24 (Box 2)
    - Community Colleges, 1987 March 24 (Box 2)
    - Department of Higher Education, 1987 March 24 (Box 2)
    - University of Connecticut Health center, 1987 March 24 (Box 2)
    - State University, 1987 March 24 (Box 2)
    - University of Connecticut, 1987 March 28 (Box 2)
    - Department of Administration Services, 1987 March 31 (Box 2)
    - Department of Housing, 1987 March 31 (Box 2)
    - Bonding Subcommittee meeting, 1987 March 31 (Box 2)
    - Capitol Restoration, 1987 March 31 (Box 2)
    - Bonding Subcommittee meeting, 1987 march 24 (Box 2)
    - Department of Revenue Services, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Commission on Human Rights, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Capitol Budget (Bond Package), 1988 (Box 2)
    - Bond Projects (Box 2)
    - Agenda items for State Bond Commission, 1988 May 27, July 22 (Box 2)
    - 1988 Bonding Information (Box 2)
    - Bond Request Proposals for FY 1988-1989 (Box 2)
    - 1988-1989 Bonding Material (Box 2)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 January 14 (Box 2)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1988 January 14 (Box 2)
    - Department of Economic Development, 1988 January 14 (Box 3)
    - Department of Agriculture, 1988 January 14 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Product Development Authority, 1988 January 14 (Box 3)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Judicial Department, 1987 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Department of Correction, 1988 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Department of Transportation, 1987 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Department of Human Resources, 1988 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Department of Children & Youth Services, 1988 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Department of Public Safety, 1988 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Department of the Military, 1988 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Department of Health Services, 1988 January 15 (Box 3)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Department of Mental Health, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Department of Mental Retardation, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Veterans Homes & Hospitals Commission, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - State Board of Education, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State Historical Commission, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Board of Education & Services to the Blind, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Alcohol & Drug Abuse Commission, `1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - State Library, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Commission on Fire Prevention & Control, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - American School for the Deaf, 1988 January 20 (Box 3)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - State Technical Colleges, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - University of Connecticut Health Center, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - State University, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - Regional Community Colleges, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - Department of Higher Education, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - University of Connecticut, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - Office of Policy & Management, 1988 January 22 (Box 3)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 January 27 (Box 3)
    - Department of Housing, 1988 January 27 (Box 3)
    - Department of Public Works, 1988 January 27 (Box 3)
    - Capitol Restoration / Legislative Management, 1988 January 27 (Box 3)
    - Bureau of Statewide Emergency Telecommunication, 1988 January 27 (Box 3)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 February 11 (Box 3)
    - Commission on the Arts, 1988 February 11 (Box 3)
    - 1988 Department of the Military, 1988 February 11 (Box 3)
    - Department of Agriculture & Regional marketing Authority, 1988 February 11 (Box 3)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1988 February 11 (Box 3)
    - Division of Special Revenue, 1988 February 11 (Box 3)
    - Department of Economic Development and Product Development Authority, 1988 February 11 (Box 3)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Department of Higher Education, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Museum of Natural History, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Central Connecticut Valley, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - University of Connecticut Health Center, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Regional Community College, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Department of Health Services, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Department of Human Resources, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Department of Public Safety & Bureau of Statewide Telecommunication, 1988 February 18 (Box 3)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 February 19 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State Library, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Commission on Fire Prevention & Control, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Historical Commission, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Eugene O'Neill Theater, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - American School for the Deaf, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Department of Administrative Services, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Public Broadcasting, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Department of Mental Health, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Alcohol and Drug Abuse Commission, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - State Board of Education, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Department of Mental Retardation, 1988 February 19 (Box 4)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 February 23 (Box 4)
    - Department of Veterans Affairs, 1988 February 23 (Box 4)
    - Department of Children and Youth Services, 1988 February 23 (Box 4)
    - Judicial Department, 1988 February 23 (Box 4)
    - Department of Corrections, 1988 February 23 (Box 4)
    - Office of Policy & Management, 1988 February 23 (Box 4)
    - Bond meeting, 1988 February 25 (Box 4)
    - Department of Public Works, 1988 February 25 (Box 4)
    - Department of Transportation, 1988 February 25 (Box 4)
    - Department of Housing, 1988 February 25 (Box 4)
    - State Technical Colleges, 1988 February 25 (Box 4)
    - Bond Commission Reports FY 1989 (Box 4)
    - Bond Commission Report Material (Box 4)
    - Wallingford Back-up (Box 4)
    - Bond Projects (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Children's Museum (Box 4)
    - April - Bond Commission (Box 4)
    - State Bond Commission Agenda, 1988 May 27 (Box 4)
    - State Bond Commission Agenda, 1988 July 7 (Box 4)
    - State Bond Commission Agenda, 1988 July 22 (Box 4)
    - State Bond Commission Agenda, 1988 September 2 (Box 4)
    - State Bond Commission Agenda, 1988 October 28 (Box 4)
    - State Bond Commission Agenda, 1988 December 2 (Box 4)
- Series 8. Board of Equalization, 1925-1927; 1999-099
  - Minutes, 1925-1927; 1 volume (Volume Unnumbered volume)
- Series 9. Public Works funds allotments, 1938-1940; 1983-003
  - Records, 1938-1940; 1 volume (Box 64)
- Series 10. Scrapbooks, 1927-1939; T003187
  Mounted newspaper clippings about state government, finances, taxation, etc.
  Variously arranged, usually chronological. Some with indexes.
  - 1927-1928, 1 volume (Volume Item 1)
  - 1928 June-1929 January, 1 volume (Volume Item 2)
  - 1929, 1 volume (Volume Item 3)
  - 1929-1930, 1 volume (Volume Item 4)
  - 1930 June-1931 January, 1 volume (Volume Item 5)
  - 1931 January-April, 1 volume (Volume Item 6)
  - 1931 May-November, 1 volume (Volume Item 7)
  - 1931-1932, 1 volume (Volume Item 8)
  - 1932 July-1933 January, 1 volume (Volume Item 9)
  - 1933, 1 volume (Volume Item 10)
  - 1933-1934, 1 volume (Volume Item 11)
  - 1935, 1 volume (Volume Item 12)
  - 1936-1938 March, 1 volume (Volume Item 13)
  - 1938-1939, 1 volume (Volume Item 14)
- Series 11. Commission on State Institutions, 1919-1948; T000685
  - Collections ledger, 1919-1948; 1 volume
- Series 12. Planning and Budgeting, circa 1971-1972; 2004-026; 22 cubic feet
  - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, 1971-1972
    - Millstone 1, Provisional Operating License No. DPR-21, Docket No. 245, Amendments, 1971-1972; 7 sets of copies (Box 1)
    - Millstone 2, Construction Permit No. CPPR-76, Docket 50-336, Amendments, 1972; 7 sets of copies (Box 2)
    - Millstone Unit No. 1, Amendments 16, 17, 18, 20, 25, 27, and 28, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, 1972; 5 copies, errata and combinations (Box 3)
    - Millstone Unit No. 1, "Various Amendments" (Sic. letter transmittal from Millstone Point Co.), 1972 (Box 3)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1 and No. 2, Amendment No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, 1972; 2 copies (Box 4)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Application for Conversion from Provisional Operating License to Full-Term Operating license, Unit No. 1, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, Appendices, Unit No. 1 & No. 2, 1972; 2 copies (Box 4)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No.; 2, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 1, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 2, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 3, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 2, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1, Environmental, Operating License Stage (Box 5)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Amendment No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 5)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage (Box 5)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 5)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, Appendixes, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 5)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, 2 copies (Box 5)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 1 (Box 5)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 2 (Box 5)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 3 (Box 5)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 5)
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 2 (Box 5)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 6)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage (Box 6)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1 and Unit 2, Amendment No.. 1, Environmental Report, operating License Stage (Box 6)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit 1 and 2 (Box 6)
    - Appendix B, Vol. 1, Millstone Unit 1 and 2 (Box 6)
    - Appendix B, Vol. 2, Millstone Unit 1 and 2 (Box 6)
    - Appendix B, Vol. 3, Millstone Unit 1 and 2 (Box 6)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit 1 and 2 (Box 6)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Amendment No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 7)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 7)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 7)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 7)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 1 (Box 7)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 2 (Box 7)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volume 3 (Box 7)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 7)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 2 (Box 7)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1 & No.; 2, Amendment No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 8)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Construction permit Stage (Box 8)
    - Milllstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 8)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 8)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 8)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, 2 copies (Box 8)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volumes 1-3 (Box 8)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 8)
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 2 (Box 8)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1, Environmental Report, Operating License State (Box 9)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Amendment No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 9)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage (Box 9)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 9)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 9)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 9)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volumes 1-3 (Box 9)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 9)